A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 1 FA1292
Rockefeller Archive Center
China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 1
1914-2002
Rockefeller Archive Center
China Medical Board (U.S.)
FA1292
61.43 Cubic Feet 127 legal size record storage boxes 3 tall legal size record storage box
Scope and Contents
Type of records include: Reports, publications, newspaper articles, correspondence, reprints, architectural drawings and maps, and photographs.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
These records are in three series, 1-Minutes and Document of Record 2-Fellowships and Grants and 3-Member and Officer Files
- Minutes and Document of Record, 1914-1973; 1
  - China Medical Board of the Rockefeller Foundation, Minutes, 1914-1920 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - China Medical Board of the Rockefeller Foundation, Minutes, 1921-1927 (Box 2, Folder 4-6)
  - China Medical Board, Inc., Minutes, 1928-1940 (Box 3, Folder 7-9)
  - China Medical Board, Inc., Minutes, 1941-1949 (Box 4, Folder 10-12)
  - China Medical Board, Inc., Minutes, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - China Medical Board, Inc., Minutes & China Medical Board of New York, Inc., Minutes, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - China Medical Board of New York, Inc., Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - China Medical Board of New York, Inc., Minutes, 1959-1962 (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
  - Documents of Record, Vol. I-VI, 1928-1933 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Documents of Record, Vol. VII-VIII, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Documents of Record, Vol. IX, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Documents of Record, Vol. X-XIX, 1937-1946 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Documents of Record, Vol. XX-XXIV, 1947-1951 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Documents of Record, Vol. XXV-XXX, 1952-1957 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Documents of Record, Vol. XXXI-XXXIV, 1958-1961 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Documents of Record, 1928-1945, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 25-30)
  - Documents of Record, 1946-1973 (Box 10, Folder 31-35)
  - Documents of Record, D. R. 169, Future Policy and Program, 1955 April 4, 1953, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Documents of Records, D. R. 71, 77, 131, 1936, 1939, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Endowment Funds, Expenditure Statistics, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Program Reports, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Corporate, Policy and Program, 1928, 1934-1936, 1941-1944, 1947-1948, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Corporate, Policy and Program, 1951, 1953-1955, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Corporate, Future Program Committee, Minutes & Report, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Fellowships and Grants, 1951-1996, 2002; 2
  - Fellowships, Completed, A-B, 1951-1960, 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Fellowships, Completed, C, 1953-1964 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Fellowships, Completed, D-H, 1953-1963 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Fellowships, Completed, I-K, 1952-1964 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Fellowships, Completed, L-O, 1952-1964 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Fellowships, Completed, P-S, 1952-1964 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Fellowships, Completed, T, 1951-1964 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Fellowships, Completed, U-Y, 1952-1963 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Fellowships, Accounts, Closed, 1926-1944, 1946-1948 (Box 12, Folder 51-52)
  - Fellowships, A-L, 1959-1964 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Fellowships, M-Y, 1960-1965 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - 76-532, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1975-1986, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - 76-532, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1975-1986, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 55A)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted-Financial material
  - 78-368, Seoul National University, Training of Technical Personnel, 1978-1982 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - 78-369, Seoul National University, Endowment Fund for Specially, Selected Individuals, etc., 1978-1986, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - 78-369, Seoul National University, Endowment Fund for Specially, Selected Individuals, etc., 1978-1986, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 57A)
  - 70-141-28, 72-266-9, Seoul National University, Fellowship, Rha, Bong-Jin, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - 72-266-11, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Fellowship, Suk, Se Il, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - 63-694-47, Seoul National University, Fellowship, Suk, Se Il, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - 72-266-21, 72-266-29, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Fellowship, Tchai, Bum-Suk, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - 66-896-39, Seoul National University, Fellowship, Yun, Dork Ro, 1965-1968 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - 66-934, 68-001, Seoul National University, Architectural Consultants, Whiting Associates International, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    Separated Materials
    Oversized Architectural Drawings
  - 66-934, 68-001, Seoul National University, Architectural Consultants, Whiting Associates International, 1968 January 15; 2014:022, SG 1:001
    Oversized Architectural Drawing
  - 66-934, 68-001, Seoul National University, Architectural Consultants, Whiting Associates International, 1967 November 14; 2014:022, SG 1:002
    oOversized Architectural Drawing
  - 66-934, 68-001, Seoul National University, Architectural Consultants, Whiting Associates International, 1967 November 10; 2014:022, SG 1:003
  - 66-934, 68-001, Seoul National University, Architectural Consultants, Whiting Associates International, 1968 February 7; 2014:022, SG 1, 004
  - 66-934, 68-001, Seoul National University, Architectural Consultants, Whiting Associates International, 1967 October; 2014:022, SG 1: 005
  - 68-026, 69-091, Seoul National University, Architectural Consultants, Whiting Associates International, 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - 70-122, Seoul National University, Architectural Consultants, Whiting Associates International, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - 71-176, Seoul National University, Architectural Consultants, Whiting Associates International, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - 72-233, Seoul National University, Architectural Consultants, Whiting Associates International, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - 68-002, 69-059, Seoul National University, Consultant, Public Health Education, Brown, Harold W., 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - 67-961, Seoul National University, Visiting Professor, Pediatrics, Fellers, Francis X., 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - 63-678, Seoul National University, Consultant, Gault, Neal L., Jr., 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - 71-182- 72-235, Seoul National University, Visiting Professor, Lee, Kwang Soo, 1970-1973 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - 71-182, 72-235, Seoul National University, Visiting Professor, Lee, Kwang Soo, 1970-1973 (Box 14, Folder 71A)
  - 66-909, Research, Anatomy-Lee, Kwang Ho, Physiology-Nam, Kee Yong, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - 67-943, Seoul National University, Research, General Correspondence, Physiology-Kim, Woo Kyeum, Parasitology-Kim, Han Jong, Biochemistry-Kim, Han Seob, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - 67-967, Seoul National University, Equipment, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - 67-968, Seoul National University, Research, Isotope Laboratory-Lee, J. K., Pharmacology-Park, C. W., Ophthalmology-Youn, W. S., Clinical Pathology-Tchai, B. S. & Kim, S. I., 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - 68-007, Seoul National University, General Correspondence, Original Requests, Hewlett Packard & Overseas Medical Supply Company, 1968-1969, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - 68-033, Seoul National University, Research, Equipment, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - 69-064, Seoul National University, Library Support, General Correspondence, Original Orders, 1969, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - 69-065, Seoul National University, Audiovisual Equipment, General Correspondence, Original Orders, 1969, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - 69-066, Seoul National University, Research, Physiology-Nam, K. Y., Clinical Pathology-Kim, S. I., Thor Surgery-Lee, Y. K., Biochemistry-Lee, K. Y. & Kim, H. S., Physiology-Kim, W. G., 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - 69-096, Seoul National University, Equipment, General Correspondence, Original Orders, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - 69-097, Seoul National University, Research, General Correspondence, Original Orders, Overseas Medical Supple Company, American Optical Corporation, 1969, 1971, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - 70-123, Seoul National University, Equipment-Physiology, General Correspondence, Original Orders, Narco Bio-Systems, Inc., Overseas Medical Company, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - 70-124, Seoul National University, Research, General Correspondence, Original Orders, 1970-1971, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - 70-151, Seoul National University, Equipment, General Correspondence, Original Orders, 1970-1973 (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - 70-152, Seoul National University, Research, General Correspondence, Original Orders, 1970-1972, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - 71-180, Seoul National University, Equipment-Student Laboratory, General Correspondence, Original Orders, 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - 71-181, Seoul National University, Research, General Correspondence, Original Orders, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - 71-210, Seoul National University, Research, General Correspondence, Original Orders, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 89)
  - 72-243 I, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Research, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 90)
  - 73-300 I, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Research, General Correspondence, Original Orders, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 91)
  - 63-716, Seoul National University, Supplies & Equipment-Teaching & Research, 1963, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 92)
  - 63-717, Seoul National University, Supplies & Equipment-Research, 1958, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - 64-777, Seoul National University, Equipment-Research, General Correspondence, Original Orders, Microbiology-Lee. Seung Hoon, Physiology-Shin, Dong Hoon, Pathology-Lee, Sang Hook, 1964-1967 (Box 15, Folder 94)
  - 65-811, Seoul National University, Equipment-Research, 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - 65-849, Seoul National University, Research-Supplies & Equipment, 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 96)
  - 66-874, Seoul National University, Research, Equipment, 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 97)
  - 66-907, Seoul National University, Library Support, 1965-1969 (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - 66-908, Seoul National University, Equipment-Teaching & Reserach, 1966-1969 (Box 15, Folder 99)
  - 71-209, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Progress Reports on Construction Bio-Medical Library, 1969, 1971-1976 (Box 15, Folder 100)
  - 72-271 I, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1975 (Box 15, Folder 101)
  - 72-272 I, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Equipment-Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - 72-273 I, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Library Support-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1973, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - 72-241, 72-270, Seoul National University, Consultant, Whiting Associates International, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 104)
  - 72-242, Seoul National University, Continuing Medical Education, 1972-1975 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - 72-244, Seoul National University, Training Tech Personnel, 1972-1976, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 106)
  - 74-332 I, Seoul National University, College of Medicine, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1974, 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 107)
  - 75-344 I, Seoul National University, Continuing Medical Education Program, 1975, 1977-1981 (Box 16, Folder 108)
  - 69-099, Kyungpook National University, Equipment, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - 70-154, Kyungpook National University, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 110)
  - 70-155, Kyungpook National University, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1972, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 111)
  - 71-212, Kyungpook National University, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1975 (Box 16, Folder 112)
  - 59-474-1, Kyungpook National University, Fellow, Choy, Chung-hun, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 113)
  - 64-762-10, Kyungpook National University, Fellow, Chung, Jae Kyu, 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 114)
  - CM 311-23, Kyungpook National University, Taegu Medical College, Fellow, Chung, Chang Soo, 1955, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 115)
  - 65-868-3, Kyungpook National University, Fellow, Chung, Tai-Ho, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 116)
  - 70-141-12, 70-141-67, Kyungpook National University, Fellow, Jo, Joon NSeung, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 117)
  - 67-936-8, Kyungpook National University, Fellow, Joo, Kang, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 118)
  - 70-141-9, Kyungpook National University, Fellow, Kim, Kyu Soo, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 119)
  - CM 362-23, Kyungpook National University, Taegu Medical School, Fellow, Kim, Soon Yong, 1956-1957, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 120)
  - CM 311-22, Kyungpook National University, Medical College, Fellow, Kim Tai Soo, 1954-1955, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 121)
  - 59-474-40, Kyungpook National University, Fellow, Kim, Tai Soo, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 122)
  - 68-022-22, Kyungpook National University, Fellow, Ko, Sung Soo, 1966, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 123)
  - CM 259-3, Kyungpook National University, School of Medicine, Fellow, Lee, Kyu Taik, 1953, 1956, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 124)
  - 64-762-56, 66-896-41, Kyungpook National University, Fellow, Ryo, Ung Yun, 1964-1965, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 125)
  - 63-694-28, Kyungpook National University, Fellow, Ryoo, Ho-Yul, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 126)
  - 70-141-31, Kyungpook National University, Fellow, Ryoo, Ho-Yul, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 127)
  - 67-936-3, 67-938-55, Kyungpook National University, Fellow, Sohn, Tae Joong, 1964-1965, 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 128)
  - 61-601, Seoul National University, Journals-General Correspondence, Walter J. Johnson, Inc., Maxwell Scientific International, Inc., 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 129)
  - 63-715, Seoul National University, Library Support, 1963-1967 (Box 16, Folder 130)
  - Cm 380, Chonnam National University, Kwan-Ju Medical College, Equipment Pre-Clinical Labs, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 131)
  - 59-482, Chonnam National University, Equipment-General Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 132)
  - 59-506, 60-524, Chonnam National University, Rehabilitation-Microbiology Lab, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 133)
  - 59-506, 60-524, Chonnam National University, Rehabilitation-Microbiology Lab, 1959-1961; 2014:022, SG 1:006
  - 59-506, 60-524, Chonnam National University, Rehabilitation-Microbiology Lab, 1959-1961; 2014:022, SG1:007
  - 59-506, 60-524, Chonnam National University, Rehabilitation-Microbiology Lab, 1959-1961; 2014:022, SG 1:008
  - 59-506, 60-524, Chonnam National University, Rehabilitation-Microbiology Lab, 1959-1961; 2014:022, SG 1:009
  - 595-474-2, Chonnam National University, Fellow, Park, Hyng Kyun, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 134)
  - CM 362-22, 57-397-12, Chonnam National University, Fellow, Chun, Doki, 1956-1958, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 135)
  - Pusan National University, General, 1957-1959, 1961-1962, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 136)
  - 59-483, Pusan National University, Books, Journals, & Equipment, 1959-1962 (Box 17, Folder 137)
  - Soo Do Medical College, General, 1957-1961, 1963-1965, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 138)
  - 58-440, Soo Do Medical College, Equipment-Departments of Nutrition & Biochemistry, General Correspondence & Fischer-Spectrophotometer, etc., 1957-1960 (Box 17, Folder 139)
  - CM 327-21, Soo Do Medical College, Fellow, Ju, Jin Soon, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 140)
  - 59-474-17, Soo Do Medical College, Fellow, Kim, Sun Wuk, 1959, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 141)
  - 57-397-41, Soo Do Medical College, Fellow, Koh, Kwang Do, 1958, 1961, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 142)
  - CM 311-27, Soo Do Medical College, Fellow, Rha, Bok Young, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 143)
  - 57-397-22, Soo Do Medical College, Fellow, song, Young Hi, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 144)
  - 59-474-3, Soo Do Medical College, Fellow, Suh, Inn Soo, 1959, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 145)
  - Kyungpook National University, Taegu Medical College, General, 1967, 1969, 1971, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 146)
  - Kyungpook National University, General Correspondence, China Medical Board Members, 1957-1959, 1962-1971 (Box 17, Folder 147)
  - Kyungpook National University, General Correspondence, Dean-Chung, Jae Kyu & Park, Hi-Myung, 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 148)
  - CM 337, Kyungpook National University, Taegu Medical College, Equipment, 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 149)
  - CM 366, Kyungpook National University, Taegu Medical College, Equipment-Photographic Materials, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 150)
  - 59-481, Kyungpook National University, Equipment-Teaching & Research, 1959-1962 (Box 17, Folder 151)
  - 62-657, Kyungpook National University, Equipment & Supplies, 1961-1965 (Box 17, Folder 152)
  - 63-718, Kyungpook National University, Equipment & Supplies, 1963-1965 (Box 17, Folder 153)
  - 664-778, Kyungpook National University, Equipment-Central Instrument Room, 1964-1965, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 154)
  - 65-812, Kyungpook National University, Supplies & Equipment, 1964-1966 (Box 17, Folder 155)
  - 65-840, Kyungpook National University, Research Equipment-Bacteriology & Radiology, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 156)
  - 65-848, Kyungpook National University, Supplies & Equipment-Instrument Repair Shop, General Correspondence & Original Orders, Overseas Medical Supply Co., 1965-1970 (Box 18, Folder 157)
  - 66-875, Kyungpook National University, Research-Biochemistry & Preventative Medicine, 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 158)
  - 66-876, Kyungpook National University, Renovation-Library & Bacteriology Lab, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 159)
  - 66-876, Kyungpook National University, Renovation-Library & Bacteriology Lab, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1966-1968; 2014:022, SG 1: 0010
    Oversized architectural drawing, Floor Plan
  - 66-876, Kyungpook National University, Renovation-Library & Bacteriology Lab, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1966-1968; 2014:022, SG1:011
    Oversized architectural drawing, Department of Bacteriology: Student Lab (Remodeling)
  - 66-876, Kyungpook National University, Renovation-Library & Bacteriology Lab, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1966-1968; 2014:022, SG1:012
    Oversized architectural drawing, Library Plan
  - 66-876, Kyungpook National University, Renovation-Library & Bacteriology Lab, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1966-1968; 2014:022, SG1:013
  - 66-876, Kyungpook National University, Renovation-Library & Bacteriology Lab, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1966-1968; 2014:022, SG1:014
    Oversized architectural drawing, Library
  - 66-877, Kyungpook National University, Equipment, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 160)
  - 66-910, Kyungpook National University, Research, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 161)
  - 67-944, Kyungpook National University, Student Laboratory Remodel-General Correspondence & Original Equipment, 1966-1969 (Box 18, Folder 162)
  - 67-944, Kyungpook National University, Student Laboratory Remodel-General Correspondence & Original Equipment, 1966-1969; 2014:022, SG1:015
    Oversized architectural drawing, Remodeling Plan of the Student Laboratories of Pharmacology, Physiology, and Pathology and Histology
  - 67-944, Kyungpook National University, Student Laboratory Remodel-General Correspondence & Original Equipment, 1966-1969; 2014:022, SG1:016
    Oversized architectural drawing, Remodeling Plan of Student Laboratories of Pharmacolofy, Physiology, and Pathology and Histology
  - 67-945, Kyungpook National University, Bacteriology-Chun, Doki, Biochemistry-Ryoo, Ho Yul, 1966-1971 (Box 18, Folder 163)
  - 67-970, Kyungpook National University, Equipment, 1967-1970 (Box 18, Folder 1967)
  - 68-009, Kyungpook National University, Research, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 165)
  - 68-034, Kyungpook National University, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1972 (Box 18, Folder 166)
  - 68-035, Kyungpook National University, Library Support-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1971, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 167)
  - 71-213, Kyungpook National University, Library Support-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 168)
  - 69-067, Kyungpook National University, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, Physiology-Chae, E. U., Biochemistry-Ryoo, Ho Yul, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 169)
  - Yonsei University, College of Medicine, General Correspondence, Dean and Staff, 1973, 1975-1977, 1979, 1981-1982, 1984-1989, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 170)
  - 72-237, Yonsei University, College of Medicine, Development Fund, 1971-1987 (Box 18, Folder 171)
  - 72-237, Yonsei University, College of Medicine, Development Fund, 1971-1987 (Box 18, Folder 171A)
  - 75-346, Yonsei University, College of Medicine, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1973, 1975-1982, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 172)
  - 85-439, Yonsei University, College of Medicine, Faculty Development Fund, 1985-1991 (Box 19, Folder 173)
  - 57-418, Yonsei University, Equipment, 1957-1961 (Box 19, Folder 174)
  - 58-469, 61-571, Yonsei University, Building Construction & Equipment, General Correspondence, 1961-1968 (Box 19, Folder 175-176)
  - 57-402, Yonsei University, Equipment-Surgical Laboratory, 1957-1958, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 177)
  - 59-507, Yonsei University, Research, 1959-1963 (Box 19, Folder 178)
  - 60-554, Yonsei University, Research-Clinical & Preclinical, 1960-1965 (Box 19, Folder 179)
  - 62-628, Yonsei University, Books-Journals-Equipment-Library Support, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 180)
  - 62-656, Yonsei University, Equipment & Supplies-Research, 1962-1966, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 181)
  - 63-712, Yonsei University, Supplies & Equipment-Basic Science Departments, 1963-1966 (Box 20, Folder 182)
  - 63-713, Yonsei University, Supplies & Equipment-Research, Clinical & Preclinical, 1963-1966 (Box 20, Folder 183)
  - 63-714, Yonsei University, Supplies-Cardio-Pulmonary Surgery, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 184)
  - 64-740, Yonsei University, Supplies & Equipment-Experimental Surgery & Animal Quarters, 1964-1965, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 185)
  - 64-769, Yonsei University, Library Support, 1964-1967 (Box 20, Folder 186)
  - 64-775, Yonsei University, Equipment-Environmental Health, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 187)
  - 64-776, Yonsei University, Equipment-Research, 1964-1967, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 188)
  - 65-808, Yonsei University, Equipment, 1965-1967 (Box 20, Folder 189)
  - 65-809, Yonsei University, Equipment-Physiology & Pharmacology, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 190)
  - 65-810, Yonsei University, Operating Microscope, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 191)
  - 65-847, Yonsei University, Supplies & Equipment-Research, 1965-1971 (Box 20, Folder 192-193)
  - 66-904, Yonsei University, Research Equipment, 1966-1969, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 194)
  - 66-905, Yonsei University, Equipment-Teaching & Research, 1965-1969 (Box 21, Folder 1995)
  - 66-906, Yonsei University, Additional Staff Salary, 1966-1967, 1969-1970, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 196)
  - 67-942, Yonsei University, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Equipment Lists, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 197)
  - 67-963, Yonsei University, Library Support, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 198)
  - 67-964, Yonsei University, Equipment, 1966-1969 (Box 21, Folder 199)
  - 67-965, Yonsei University, Electron Microscope, 1967-1970 (Box 21, Folder 200)